<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-04-21T23:41:38-04:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">gregore</title><subtitle>art and stuff</subtitle><author><name>grub</name></author><entry><title type="html">July 2020</title><link href="/writing/July-2020.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="July 2020" /><published>2020-07-31T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-31T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>/writing/July-2020</id><content type="html" xml:base="/writing/July-2020.html">&lt;p&gt;A radio antenna shifted and plunged me into static.&lt;br /&gt;
I turned it off weeks ago, but I still hear the buzzing.&lt;br /&gt;
I think it’ll end soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see a heat haze, my vision fuzzing.&lt;br /&gt;
Was it this dark outside when I closed my eyes, or is this the right time to wake up?&lt;br /&gt;
The lightbulbs twitch and it’s a week later.&lt;br /&gt;
They’re mowing the lawn again.&lt;br /&gt;
They did it yesterday or two weeks ago, but I still hear the humming.&lt;br /&gt;
I think it’ll stop soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just two more minutes.&lt;br /&gt;
Just two more days.&lt;br /&gt;
Just two more months.&lt;br /&gt;
The static noise pulsates, but only when I tune into it–it’s rhythmic when I hear the rhythms, but when’s the last time I did?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it’ll be over soon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>grub</name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">A radio antenna shifted and plunged me into static. I turned it off weeks ago, but I still hear the buzzing. I think it’ll end soon. I see a heat haze, my vision fuzzing. Was it this dark outside when I closed my eyes, or is this the right time to wake up? The lightbulbs twitch and it’s a week later. They’re mowing the lawn again. They did it yesterday or two weeks ago, but I still hear the humming. I think it’ll stop soon. Just two more minutes. Just two more days. Just two more months. The static noise pulsates, but only when I tune into it–it’s rhythmic when I hear the rhythms, but when’s the last time I did?</summary></entry></feed>